pets2play.com 2014-01-05

# 

Pets2play.com is single-mindedly devoted in proffering a service, which is but an amusing, fun-filled as well as an educational service. Pets2play.com pays sincere attention towards the privacy concerns of the visitors, who pay a visit to Pets2play.com 

**Information Gathering - How they are put to use**

As the visitors pay a visit to Pets2play.com, we at Pets2play.com collect certain information with the help of the cookies, and also from that of the traffic references which can be sought from the hosting servers. 

Traffic References available from the hosting servers – Information of certain type is made available as a visitor makes a visit to a website, made available by the visitor, for gathering purpose, which include the internet domain, the time pertaining to the visit, location, IP address, operating system that has been used in establishing access to Pets2play.com, pages that get visited by the visitor, in case the visitor is linked to Pets2play.com from some other website and also the address that pertains to the website, the browser type, and other such relevant details. At Pets2play.com, we gather such details as practiced by the other operators, and make use of the collected information as that of visitors' statistics and in improving the services rendered to the users. 

From Cookies- The prime purpose of putting the cookies to use is aimed to enhance the online experience of the visitors. Cookies are but small files, which are stored on the computers, and which happens through the means of websites. Through web browser pertaining to that of the user, the website which writes the cookies puts these cookies to use. The access to the data that gets collected in a cookie from Pets2play.com can only be established by Pets2play.com. The information gathered helps in the running of the affiliate programs, permits customized advertising, and also the automatic signing in of the user is made possible as the user pays a visit to Pets2play.com, and allows other kinds of operational site activities. Mostly, browsers have been set in a way so as to accept the cookies. The resetting related to the browser can be done that suits your preferences as in a way it allows you to know as when a cookie gets received, or the resetting can be done in a way so as to refuse the cookies. In any event, the user should be aware of the fact that some parts pertaining to Pets2play.com can be viewed only if the user’s browser permits cookies. 

We at Pets2play.com do not endeavor to share information that is provided by the user with anyone. If disclosure of such type is wanted by the law enforcement or even by the government officials of other types, it is an exception as the information wanted gets linked to investigation pertaining to fraudulent activities, for infringement regarding intellectual property or other kinds of illegal activities, or that which could expose us or which could expose you as related with legal liability. 

**Collection of Information, Third-Party Sites and Sponsors**

It is of paramount importance to understand as well as to know that the links that get established to Pets2play.com by advertisers or that of other sites might collect information related to the users. The Privacy Policy of Pets2play.com doesn’t limit the activities of advertisers or other sites, and cannot be applied to the advertisers or other sites. The third-party advertising companies are made use of by Pets2play.com for serving ads on the user’s website. The information may be put to use by these companies as related to the visits made by the user to Pets2play.com as well as to other sites, and as a means in providing them with ads of relevant types to the user. The cookies might get placed or even read by the third parties on the user’s browser, or the web beacons may be put to use for collecting information, further to the ads that are served on the user’s website. If the user doesn’t want the placing of the cookies as well as to be read by the third parties, the browser related to the user can be set in such a way as to block them. 

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information,browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit www.networkadvertising.org. 

**Google Adsense**

As a third-party vendor, Google puts the cookies to use in serving ads on the user’s site. 

The DART cookies are put to use by Google in serving ads for the users, which gets based upon the users’ visits to your site and also to other sites that can be found on the internet. 

Users can opt out of the usage pertaining to DART cookie by paying a visit to the Google ad and content network privacy policy . 

**Security**

At Pets2play.com, the data gathered is stored in the database servers related to Pets2play.com, as it could be one or more of database servers. Reasonable precautions are undertaken at Pets2play.com in securing the data, but, as a user, you should take note of the fact that the internet is not 100% safe, owing to which, we at Pets2play.com do not issue guarantee concerning the safety of the information that is provided by the user. All kinds of transmission are undertaken by you at your sole risk. 

**Links - To Other Sites**

At Pets2play.com, we establish links to other sites. As and when a user establishes link to another site, the user ceases to be on our website, and gets subjected to the Privacy Policy related to the linked site. 

**Agreement with Pets2play.com Policies**

By putting Pets2play.com to use, you express your assent to the Privacy Policy of Pets2play.com. If the policy doesn’t meet your approval, do not make use of Pets2play.com. We at Pets2play.com hold the rights towards executing changes to the policy, at time chosen as by our accord. As you make a visit to Pets2play.com each time, check with the policy section every time, so as to be sure of the changes incorporated to the policy section. 

We partner with ValueClick to serve ads and/or collect certain information when you visit our website. ValueClick may use cookies or web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information during your visit to this website in order to help show advertisements on other websites likely to be more interesting to you. To learn more about this “behavioral advertising” practice or to opt-out of this use of your anonymous information, you can visit http://valueclickmedia.com/member_privacy.shtml
